const koreanQuestions = [
  {
    question: '「사랑」 の意味は？',
    options: ['愛', '夢', '友情', '命'],
    answer: '愛',
  },
  {
    question: '「학교」 の意味は？',
    options: ['図書館', '学校', '教室', '塾'],
    answer: '学校',
  },
  {
    question: '「친구」 の意味は？',
    options: ['先生', '兄弟', '友達', '親戚'],
    answer: '友達',
  },
  {
    question: '「음악」 の意味は？',
    options: ['歌詞', '音楽', '絵', '舞台'],
    answer: '音楽',
  },
  {
    question: '「날씨」 の意味は？',
    options: ['天気', '空気', '気温', '曇り'],
    answer: '天気',
  },
  {
    question: '「물」 の意味は？',
    options: ['ジュース', '氷', '水', 'お茶'],
    answer: '水',
  },
  {
    question: '「고양이」 の意味は？',
    options: ['犬', '猫', 'うさぎ', '鳥'],
    answer: '猫',
  },
  {
    question: '「행복」 の意味は？',
    options: ['努力', '幸せ', '愛情', '成功'],
    answer: '幸せ',
  },
  {
    question: '「시간」 の意味は？',
    options: ['曜日', '部屋', '時間', '時代'],
    answer: '時間',
  },
  {
    question: '「가족」 の意味は？',
    options: ['祖先', '兄弟', '親友', '家族'],
    answer: '家族',
  },
];

export { koreanQuestions };